Tufts Topics UP003
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts Topics
1943 -- 1946
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts University Alumni Association
UP003
1 Volumes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of bound issues of the alumni magazine, Tufts Topics. Tufts Topics called itself a "duration publication aimed exclusively at the thousands of graduates and former students scattered over the globe in the service of the nation." Thus the format was typewritten text on thin paper, with few pictures, all to save paper and postage costs. The news was generally about events on campus and the journeys of Tufts graduates in the armed forces.
Tufts Topics emphatically declared that "Tufts Topics will never appeal to you for funds... we are in existence only to serve you [Tufts graduates in the Armed Forces]."
Related Materials
UP004, Tufts Alumni Review, DCA
UP052, Tufts Magazine, DCA
UP053, Tufts Criterion, DCA
UP065, Tufts Review, DCA
- Tufts Topics, 1943 -- 1946; UP003.001; 1 Volumes
  Scope and Contents
  Bound issues of the alumni magazine, Tufts Topics. Tufts Topics called itself a "duration publication aimed exclusively at the thousands of graduates and former students scattered over the globe in the service of the nation." Thus the format was typewritten text on thin paper, with few pictures, all to save paper and postage costs. The news was generally about events on campus and the journeys of Tufts graduates in the armed forces. An alumni magazine, Tufts Topics was designed for Tufts graduates serving in the armed forces during World War II. It replaced the Tufts College Alumni Magazine in 1943. Tufts Topics was itself replaced by the Tufts Alumni Review in 1947.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Tufts Topics, volume 1, number 1, 1943-09; UP003.001.001.00001 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 2, 1943-10; UP003.001.001.00002 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 3, 1943-12; UP003.001.001.00003 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 4, 1944-01; UP003.001.001.00004 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 5, 1944-02; UP003.001.001.00005 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 6, 1944-03; UP003.001.001.00006 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 7, 1944-04; UP003.001.001.00007 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 8, 1944-05; UP003.001.001.00008 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 1, number 9, 1944-06; UP003.001.001.00009 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 1, 1944-09; UP003.001.001.00010 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 2, 1945-12; UP003.001.001.00011 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 3, 1945-01; UP003.001.001.00012 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 4, 1945-03; UP003.001.001.00013 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 5, 1945-04; UP003.001.001.00014 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 2, number 6, 1945-05; UP003.001.001.00015 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 1, 1945-09; UP003.001.001.00016 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 2, 1945-12; UP003.001.001.00017 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 3, 1946-01; UP003.001.001.00018 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 4, 1946-03; UP003.001.001.00019 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 5, 1946-04; UP003.001.001.00020 (Box Volume 1)
  - Tufts Topics volume 3, number 6, 1946-07; UP003.001.001.00021 (Box Volume 1)